Can this boy called Conan Edogawa...
Bisakah kita benar-benar mempercayai...
really be trusted?
Conan Edogawa ini?
He does seem to be a bit sharp, though.
Dia tampak cukup pintar.
Don't worry.
Itu akan baik-baik saja.
And? When is this boy coming here?
Dan? Kapan dia akan datang ke sini?
The promised time is...
Dia seharusnya...
It's about time.
tiba sebentar lagi.
I hope you made sure that he'd come alone?
Kau menyuruhnya untuk datang sendirian, bukan?
Yeah.
Ya.
I made sure that he wouldn't bring the children along.
Aku mengingatkan dia untuk tidak mengundang anak-anak itu.
There he is, he's come.
Dia di sini.
Make sure to carry things out with great care.
Hati-hati.
If they're people who aren't worth it,
Jika dia tidak sepadan dengan waktu kita,
we're getting out of here
maka kita akan harus meninggalkan tempat ini
and gotta find a new base to operate from.
dan menemukan markas operasi baru.
Yeah, I know.
Ya, aku tahu.
Go hide in the bathroom until you're convinced.
Sembunyilah di kamar kecil hingga kau yakin.
Yes, coming.
Datang.
I have been waiting for you, Conan.
Aku sudah menunggumu, Conan.
Yahoo!
Hei!
We came along, too.
Kami datang dengannya.
You... you didn't come alone?
Kau... kau tidak datang sendirian?
Oh, yes.
Ya.
When I told them that you told me
Ketika aku memberitahu mereka kau menyebutkan
there's a pool in this hotel,
hotel ini memiliki kolam,
they insisted on coming along.
mereka juga mau ikut.
Weren't we supposed to come?
Haruskah kami tidak datang?
Oh, no.
Oh, tidak.
It's just that I was a bit surprised
Aku hanya terkejut
because I didn't know you were coming.
karena aku tidak diberitahu.
Okay, then. You guys go on ahead to the pool.
Baiklah. Kalian pergi dulu ke kolam.
I'll get ready and be right over.
Aku akan bersiap dan menuju ke sana.
-Okay. -Okay.
-Baik. -Baik.
Sorry.
Maaf.
You idiot.
Bodoh.
Let's use the years we walked together as a springboard
Didorong maju oleh tahun yang dihabiskan bersama.
and move forward full speed without slowing down.
Maju dengan kecepatan penuh tanpa memperlambat kecepatan.
Shattered pieces of glass in the pool.
Pecahan kaca di dalam kolam.
A strange sound to a blind case.
Sebuah suara aneh terdengar selama insiden yang tak terlihat itu.
He sees through the one and only truth.
Dia melihat satu-satunya kebenaran.
A child in appearance with the I.Q. of an adult.
Memiliki penampilan seorang anak kecil dengan kepintaran orang dewasa.
His name is Detective Conan!
Namanya adalah Detektif Conan!
"Mystery Sinks into the Summer Pool (Part 1)"
"Misteri Tenggelam dalam Kolam Pertengahan Musim Panas (Bagian 1)"
How spacious.
Itu besar.
Well, it's maybe a bit smaller than the pool at my villa though.
Tapi itu sedikit lebih kecil dari kolam villaku.
I mean, how big is your villa anyway?
Seberapa besar villamu?
I can't wait to see Ms. Sera's swimsuit.
Aku sangat senang akan melihat Nn. Sera dalam pakaian renang.
I wonder what kind of swimsuit it'll be.
Aku penasaran apa yang akan dia kenakan.
Well...
Yah...
A sporty one-piece swimsuit maybe?
Mungkin pakaian renang satu potong?
You're looking forward to it too, aren't you, Conan?
Bukankah kau juga senang, Conan?
Oh, yes.
Uh, ya.
As far as I'm concerned I'm more than satisfied already, though.
Aku sudah lebih dari puas.
Well, but Sera's got a flat chest.
Tapi Sera dadanya cukup datar.
Sera?
Sera?
Well, she looks like a cute younger sister, doesn't she?
Bukankah dia tampak seperti adik perempuan yang manis?
I guess so.
Kurasa.
I'm fine with "Sera".
"Sera" baik-baik saja.
I was called that when I was little, too.
Mereka memanggilku begitu ketika aku masih kecil.
Stripe bikini.
Bikini bergaris.
You don't have chest,
Kau tidak punya dada,
but you've got guts.
tapi kau punya nyali.
Guts?
Nyali?
Huh? Lady Sonoko?
Eh? Nona Sonoko?
Long time no see.
Sudah lama tidak berjumpa.
Do I know you?
Siapa kau?
"Raito Samaki (30)" -I'm Samaki, secretary for President Oiso.
"Samaki Raito (30)" -Aku Samaki, Sekretaris Presiden Oiso.
Oh, right. Maybe I met you at a party several times?
Oh, ya. Kita sudah bertemu di beberapa pesta, bukan?
You remember me.
Kau ingat.
Thank you very much.
Terima kasih.
Samaki!
Samaki!
Will you come over here a minute, Samaki?
Kemarilah, Samaki.
Yes, right now.
Segera.
Who's that girl?
Siapa dia?
She's the daughter of President Oiso that was just mentioned.
Putri dari Presiden Oiso yang baru saja kita sebutkan.
Lady Nagami Oiso.
Nona Nagami Oiso.
"Nagami Oiso (31), President's Daughter"
"Nagami Oiso (31), Putri Presiden"
Oiso? Do you mean Oiso Finance?
Oiso? Maksudmu Oiso Finance?
Yes. They're a subsidiary
Ya. Sejujurnya, mereka hanya
of our affiliate company.
satu dari anak perusahaan kami.
Yeah...
Ya...
What is it?
Ada apa?
Will you put oil on for me?
Bisakah kau oleskan minyak di tubuhku?
I let her do it for me, and she scratches me with her nails.
Aku membiarkan dia menanganinya, tapi dia mencakarku.
I... I'm sorry.
Maaf... maafkan aku.
Then, who's the one that's obsequiously bowing?
Siapa yang sedang menunduk kepadanya?
I think she's Nagami's younger sister.
Itu adik perempuan Nagami,
"Hamaka Oiso (28), Nagami's half-sister" -Lady Hamaka.
"Hamaka Oiso (28), Adik Tiri Nagami" -Nona Hamaka.
Her younger sister.
Jadi mereka adalah saudara.
She's acting too obsequiously to be her younger sister.
Bukankah dia bersikap terlalu patuh untuk seorang adik?
You can say that again.
Ya.
I heard that she's the daughter of the president's mistress.
Dia adalah putri dari seorang wanita simpanan.
Since her mother died of an illness.
Ibunya meninggal karena sakit,
It seems she had no other choice but to stay at the Oiso residence.
jadi keluarga Oiso harus membawanya.
And the one behind her younger sister
Pria yang berdiri di belakangnya
is the hired manager of this hotel.
adalah manajer hotel.
"Ensaku Toyoshima (56)" -I think his was called Mr. Toyoshima.
"Ensaku Toyoshima (56)" -Toyoshima, kurasa.
"Hotel Manager" -The owner of this hotel is President Oiso.
"Manajer Hotel" -Presiden Oiso memiliki hotel ini,
I guess he's showing people around the pool that's just been renovated.
jadi mungkin dia menunjukkan pada mereka kolam yang baru diperbaharui.
You're good. I like it.
Kau hebat. Itu dia.
You sure do it differently from the one who was doing it before you.
Kau tidak seperti pria yang mencoba ini lebih dulu.
I'm not used to doing things like this.
Aku tidak terbiasa pada hal semacam ini.
Well, I guess it comes as no surprise that you're good.
Mungkin tak heran kau sangat handal.
I guess you're rubbing oil all over for her, too.
Aku yakin kau mengoleskan minyak di seluruh tubuhnya juga.
Just what do you mean by that?
Apa maksudmu?
I've known for some time that you two were on intimate terms.
Aku tahu kau berdua berhubungan intim.
And that you both eventually plan
Aku tahu kalian juga berencana
to get a hold of half of my father's inheritance.
untuk mengambil setengah kekayaan ayahku.
No, we don't.
Tidak.
Lady Nagami, I think you're over thinking things.
Nona, bukankah menurutmu kau terlalu berpikir berlebihan?
Shut up!
Diam!
I know that you're letting the two
Aku tahu kau diam-diam membiarkan mereka
use this hotel for their rendezvous.
menggunakan hotel ini untuk kencan mereka.
I hope you haven't forgotten
Aku harap kau tidak lupa
that you're my fiance.
bahwa kau adalah tunanganku.
What?
Apa?
I'm going to talk to father about.
Bagaimanapun, aku akan memberitahu ayah tentang ini.
Nagami...
Kakak...
I don't want to hear excuses.
Aku tidak ingin mendengar alasanmu.
No, the necklace that you were wearing...
Sebenarnya, kalungmu...
No...
Tidak mungkin...
You were swimming just now.
Kau baru saja berenang.
Could it be in the pool?
Mungkinkah ada di dalam kolam?
Hey! No, just how much do you think it cost?
Apa? Tidak, kau tahu berapa nilainya itu?
Get the guests out of the pool right this minute
Usir para tamu keluar dari kolam
and close this place off.
dan tutup area ini.
-What? -What?
-Apa? -Apa?
Don't forget to check the belongings of the guests, too.
Jangan lupa untuk memeriksa tas para tamu juga.
Somebody could've secretly taken it, you see.
Seseorang mungkin telah mencurinya.
But...
Tapi...
Raito, you bring the snorkels.
Raito, bawakan aku peralatan snorkeling.
What? You mean you're going to look for it yourself?
Apa? Kau akan mencarinya sendiri?
Maybe it'll be better to drain the water of the pool, then.
Bukankah akan lebih cepat untuk mengeringkan kolamnya?
Stupid.
Dasar bodoh.
What if it goes out the drain together with the water?
Bagaimana jika masuk ke saluran air?
At any rate, get the guests out of here and look for it!
Usir para tamu keluar agar kita bisa mencarinya!
Understand?
Mengerti?
No good.
Tidak ada gunanya.
Snorkeling won't do.
Aku takkan pernah menemukannya dengan snorkeling.
Samaki, get me the oxygen tank for diving.
Samaki, bawakan aku tangki menyelam.
Okay.
Baik.
I thought that you'd say,
Aku pikir kau mungkin akan mengatakan itu,
so I already brought it here.
jadi aku sudah bawa satu.
And you.
Dan kau.
You're getting in the way of the search, so will you get out of the pool.
Kau menghalangi pencarianku, jadi keluarlah dari kolam.
But, Lady Nagami,
Tapi, nona,
I think it's faster if we all look for it together.
bukankah akan lebih cepat jika kami semua membantu?
Enough. Shut up.
Oh, diamlah.
Oh, you're getting on my nerves!
Ini sangat menyebalkan!
I'll look for it myself, so all of you get out of the pool!
Aku akan mencarinya sendiri, jadi semuanya keluarlah!
Gosh, I wonder if all rich girls are selfish like her?
Aduhai, apa semua gadis kaya itu egois?
Sonoko's not like that, right?
Sonoko, kau berbeda, bukan?
Well, I guess not.
Yah, ya.
"Lunch menu: Burgundy-style Curry Stew" -Thank you very much.
"Menu makan siang: Curry Stew ala Burgundy" -Terima kasih.
I'm sorry.
Maaf.
You guys wanted to have fun at the pool
Kita ingin bermain di kolam,
and yet to have something like that happen.
tapi kemudian itu terjadi.
It's not your fault, Ms. Sera.
Itu bukan salahmu, Nn. Sera.
It's Sera. Sera.
Itu Sera, ingat? Sera.
Well, I guess at least the hotel lunch was good so all is well.
Aku rasa tidak apa-apa karena makan siang hotelnya sangat enak.
I guess so.
Ya.
Is something wrong, Conan?
Apa ada sesuatu, Conan?
Yes. The bellboys of the hotel
Yah. Pelayan hotel itu
have been moving around busily from a while ago.
tampak sedang kebingungan.
I wonder if something happened?
Apa sesuatu terjadi?
What?
Apa?
Lady Nagami...
Nona Nagami...
Disappeared?
Menghilang?
Wasn't she looking for her necklace in the pool?
Bukankah dia sedang mencari kalungnya di dalam kolam?
She was supposed to be,
Aku pikir begitu,
but she suddenly disappeared.
tapi dia tiba-tiba menghilang.
I looked for her in the restroom and changing room near the pool, too.
Kami sudah mencari di ruang ganti dan kamar mandi di sebelah kolam.
It doesn't seem she went home either.
Dia juga belum pulang.
Hey, look!
Hei, itu!
There's something in the water in the center of the pool.
Lihat. Ada sesuatu di tengah kolam.
What?
Apa?
Isn't... isn't that...
Apa... apa itu...
a person?
orang?
Lady...
Nona...
Nagami?
Nagami?
Hey, look!
Hei, itu!
There's something in the water in the center of the pool.
Lihat. Ada sesuatu di tengah kolam.
What?
Apa?
Isn't... isn't that...
Apa... apa itu...
a person?
orang?
Lady...
Nona...
Nagami?
Nagami?
No way!
Mustahil!
How could that be?
Tak mungkin.
Nagami?
Nona?
Hurry, call the ambulance and the police!
Cepat telepon ambulan dan polisi!
-Yes! -Yes.
-Baik! -Baik.
Nagami?
Nona?
Get a hold of yourself.
Bertahanlah.
Nagami!
Nagami!
But it's odd.
Itu aneh.
There was nothing in the pool
Tidak ada apapun di dalam kolam
when we looked ten minutes ago.
ketika kami melihatnya sepuluh menit yang lalu.
You're right.
Ya.
That hurts!
Aduh!
What... what is it?
Apa... apa ini?
Shattered pieces of glass at the bottom of the pool.
Ada pecahan kaca di dasar kolam.
Shattered pieces...
Pecahan...
Glass?
Kaca?
Drowned?
Apa dia tenggelam?
Yes. According to the report of the forensic officer,
Ya. Menurut laporan koroner,
the ETD was between 12:00 to 13:00.
dia tewas antara siang dan jam 1 siang.
But I don't get it.
Aku tidak mengerti.
This pool isn't that deep that your feet don't touch the bottom, is it?
Kolam ini cukup dangkal untuk berdiri.
Yet, why'd she drown?
Bagaimana dia tenggelam?
On top of carrying the oxygen tank,
Dia mengenakan tangki
she wearing weights around her hips,
dan pemberat pada pinggulnya
so that she wouldn't come floating up.
agar dia tidak mengapung.
Lady Nagami said that she wanted to concentrate on
Nona Nagami bilang dia ingin fokus
searching the bottom of the pool.
mencari di kolam.
Lady?
Nona?
The victim is...
Korban adalah...
the daughter of the President of Oiso Finance, Nagami Oiso.
Nagami Oiso, putri dari presiden Oiso Finance.
The daughter of a president?
Putri presiden, ya?
And? What was she looking for at the bottom of the pool?
Dan? Apa yang sedang dia lakukan di dasar kolam?
She was looking for her necklace.
Dia sedang mencari kalungnya.
We noticed that it was missing when I was rubbing suntan oil on her.
Kami menyadarinya hilang selagi mengoleskan minyak padanya.
We figured she may have dropped it in the pool when she was swimming.
Kami pikir dia mungkin menjatuhkannya selagi berenang di kolam.
After we asked the guests to leave the pool.
Begitu kami sudah mengevakuasi para tamu dari kolam,
The four of us, including Lady Nagami,
kami berempat, termasuk Nona Nagami,
checked the restroom and the changing room
mencari di kamar mandi, ruang ganti,
and inside the pool.
dan kolam.
Nagami said that she wanted to look for it alone.
Tapi kakakku bilang dia ingin mencari sendirian.
So, we did as we were told...
Kami menuruti dia...
but she ended up like this.
dan kemudian ini terjadi.
I see.
Begitu.
If so, this could've been an accident.
Jadi mungkin itu sebuah kecelakaan.
Yes.
Ya.
It's probable that an accident like leg cramps caused her to panic,
Mungkin dia mengalami kecelakaan
on top of the fact that she was wearing heavy weights.
selagi mengenakan pemberat itu.
Then if the mouthpiece she used to breathe in air came off,
Jika dia panik dan kehilangan alat pernafasannya,
she could've drowned.
dia bisa tenggelam.
I don't think so.
Aku rasa tidak.
-What? -What?
-Apa? -Apa?
They said there was nothing in the pool ten minutes
Mereka bilang tidak ada apapun di dalam kolam sepuluh menit
before she was found.
sebelum dia ditemukan.
Right, sir?
Benar, pelayan?
Oh, yeah.
Ya.
Is that true?
Apa itu benar?
The manager and two others plus both of us
Mereka bertiga dan kami berdua
came to this pool to look for Lady Nagami.
datang ke kolam untuk mencari Nona Nagami,
But we couldn't find her.
tapi kami tidak menemukan dia.
And when we came to look for her again ten minutes later.
Ketika kami kembali sepuluh menit kemudian,
Lady Nagami was sunk at the bottom of the pool.
dia berada di dasar kolam.
Do you know about what time it was?
Kau tahu kapan itu?
I think it was a little after two in the afternoon.
Kurasa setelah pukul 2 siang.
Hey, I thought you said that the ETD
Bukankah dia tewas
was between 12:00 to 13:00?
antara siang dan jam 1 siang?
Yes.
Ya.
If so, after drowning Nagami between 12:00 to 13:00,
Yang artinya setelah menenggelamkan dia sekitar pukul 1 siang,
somebody hid her corpse somewhere.
seseorang menyembunyikan tubuhnya di suatu tempat.
And at about 14:00 without being seen by anyone,
Dan pukul 2 siang, mereka menenggelamkan tubuhnya
brought her to the center of the pool and sunk her.
di tengah kolam tanpa terlihat.
Right?
Benar?
Was it possible for someone to have done that unnoticed?
Apa mungkin bagi seseorang untuk melakukan itu tanpa diketahui?
No. All of us spilt up to go look for her.
Tidak. Kami berpencar untuk mencarinya,
So I think it wouldn't have been possible to not be noticed by us.
jadi aku ragu itu mungkin.
Besides, at the entrance of this pool,
Di samping itu, ada resepsionis di pintu masuk kolam
the receptionists at the counter
dan karyawati disana
are checking who goes in and out.
memeriksa semua orang yang masuk dan keluar.
I don't think they'd let anyone suspicious through.
Aku rasa mereka tidak melihat siapapun yang mencurigakan.
But...
Tapi...
it seems that something strange was at the bottom of the pool too.
ada sesuatu yang aneh di dasar kolam.
Something strange?
Sesuatu yang aneh?
There were a lot of shattered pieces of glass at the bottom of the pool,
Ada pecahan kaca di bawah kolam.
you stepped on it
Kau menginjaknya
and hurt the sole of your feet, right, manager?
dan melukai dasar kakimu. Benarkan, Pak manajer?
Yeah.
Ya.
Is... is that true?
Apa... apa itu benar?
I carried Lady Nagami's oxygen tank
Aku membawa tangkinya Nona Nagami
to the pool side,
ke pinggir kolam,
but when I was about to come out of the water with it.
tapi ketika aku berusaha untuk keluar.
That hurts!
Aduh!
I felt a surge of pain on the sole of my foot,
Aku merasakan tusukan di bawah kakiku.
and dove in to look.
Ketika aku melihat ke bawah air,
A lot of shattered glass was at the bottom of the pool.
aku melihat pecahan kaca di dasar.
What... what did you say?
Apa... apa kau kata?
Drain the water of the pool immediately.
Keringkan kolamnya.
We'll talk after that.
Kita akan bicara setelahnya.
Yes, sir!
Ya, tuan!
These do look to be shattered pieces of glass.
Mereka jelas seperti pecahan kaca.
But why are there so many?
Tapi kenapa ada banyak?
Were these here when you were searching the pool with Ms. Nagami?
Apa ini ada di sini ketika kau mencari dengan Nn. Nagami?
No.
Tidak.
There weren't any.
Tidak ada.
If there were, we'd notice.
Kami akan menyadarinya jika ada.
But with so much shattered,
Dengan semua potongan ini,
we'd have to put them back together
kita takkan tahu apa bentuk aslinya
to find out what it originally was.
kecuali kita memperbaikinya.
True.
Kau benar.
-It's an aquarium. -It's an aquarium.
-Itu sebuah akuarium. -Itu sebuah akuarium.
An aquarium?
Sebuah akuarium?
You see, the piece that you're holding now
Ada empat potongan sudut
looks like the corner of a box.
seperti yang sedang kau pegang,
And the L-shaped piece that Inspector Megure is holding.
dan empat potongan berbentuk L seperti yang
There are four each of them, right?
sedang Inspektur Megure pegang, kan?
True.
Kau benar.
There are four each.
Ada empat untuk masing-masing.
If you assemble them in your head,
Sambungkan bersama di kepalamu,
you get something that looks like an aquarium, right?
dan kau mendapatkan sebuah akuarium, kan?
I see.
Begitu.
This is making less and less sense.
Ini semakin tidak masuk akal.
Why would an aquarium be at the bottom of the pool
Kenapa ada sebuah akuarium di dalam kolam,
and much less shattered to pieces?
terlebih lagi yang sudah pecah?
Inspector Megure.
Inspektur.
We found a long fishing line stuck in the drain of the pool.
Ada tali pancing yang panjang tersangkut pada saluran air.
A fishing line?
Tali pancing?
Yes. I think it's about fifty meters.
Ya. Sekitar 50 meter panjangnya.
Why would such a thing be there?
Apa yang dilakukannya di sana?
Ms. Hamaka!
Nn. Hamaka!
What kind of necklace did Ms. Nagami lose?
Seperti apa kalung Nn. Nagami yang hilang?
A necklace with a lot of diamonds on it.
Ada banyak berliannya.
If so, the perp probably by using the pieces of glass
Mungkin pelaku berusaha untuk melakukan sesuatu
and the fishing line tried making a fake version of the necklace
dengan menciptakan ulang kalung itu
in order to do something.
dengan tali pancing dan kaca.
I think the fishing line is much too long for something like that.
Tali pancingnya tampak sedikit panjang untuk itu.
What if you make a loop at the end of the line
Kau bisa simpul ujungnya
and put the pieces of glass on it.
dan pasangkan pecahan kaca.
Then, pull it through the water in order to lure Ms. Nagami?
Mungkin mereka menariknya ke suatu tempat dengan menariknya melalui air.
I... I guess if so it's probable.
Aku... aku rasa itu tidak mustahil.
Then, please continue searching inside the pool.
Terus periksa kolamnya.
Yes, sir.
Ya, tuan.
In the meantime, let's ask for the details.
Sementara, kami akan tanya
The sequence of events that lead to the search of the necklace.
bagaimana mereka berakhir mencari kalung itu.
Let's ask those three that have a connection with Ms. Nagami.
Ketiga individual itu terkait dengan Nn. Nagami.
All three of you...
Jadi kalian semua...
put oil on Ms. Nagami?
mengoleskan minyak pada Nn. Nagami?
Yes. But she said that I wasn't good at it and turned me down.
Ya, tapi dia bilang aku buruk dan menyuruhku untuk berhenti.
Enough already. You're terrible.
Itu cukup. Kau buruk.
I seem to have scratched her with my nails and gotten her angry.
Aku tidak sengaja mencakar dia dan membuat dia marah.
That hurts. What's with you scratching me?
Aduh! Kenapa kau mencakarku?
I'm the last one who put oil on her.
Aku yang terakhir melakukannya.
But after she found out that she lost her necklace,
Tapi dia menyadari kalungnya hilang
the rubbing oil bit was dropped.
dan aku berhenti.
Nagami.
Kakak.
The necklace that you were wearing...
Kalungmu...
No...
Tidak mungkin...
You were swimming just now.
Kau baru saja berenang.
Could it be in the pool?
Mungkinkah ada di dalam kolam?
Hey! No, just how much do you think it cost?
Apa? Tidak, kau tahu berapa nilainya itu?
Get the guests out of the pool right this minute
Usir para tamu keluar dari kolam
and close this place off.
dan tutup area ini.
-What? -What?
-Apa? -Apa?
I thought it would be possible to take off her necklace
Kupikir mungkin untuk melepaskan kalungnya
while rubbing suntan oil on her.
selagi mengoleskan minyak padanya.
We had no idea that she made all three of you put suntan oil on her.
Tapi kalian bertiga melakukannya.
She favored doing things like that.
Kakakku suka hal semacam itu.
-What? -What?
-Apa? -Apa?
She would make men zip her clothes up.
Dia menyuruh pria menutup bagian belakang gaunnya.
Or make them check her temperature
Dia akan menyuruhmu menyentuh dahinya
by having them place their hands on her forehead.
karena dia merasa demam.
It was cute the way she enjoyed
Caranya imut bagaimana dia menikmati
watching people's reactions.
melihat reaksi orang-orang.
Cute?
Itu imut?
She's the type that girls don't like.
Aku yakin gadis lain membencinya.
Are girls like that?
Apa perempuan seperti itu?
But you're a girl too, aren't you, Ms. Sera?
Nn. Sera, kau juga perempuan.
It's Sera. Sera.
Itu Sera. Sera.
Oh, right.
Benar.
Of course, I knew that she would say she'd go and look for it alone.
Biasanya, aku tahu dia akan bersikeras mencarinya sendirian.
Because she was picky about everything.
Karena dia pilih-pilih tentang segala hal.
Well, I accepted that part of her thinking
Aku menerima keegoisannya
that it was her individuality though.
sebagai bagian dari dirinya.
I see.
Begitu.
But Ms. Nagami mentioned, didn't she?
Tapi bukankah Nn. Nagami bilang
That Mr. Samaki, her fiance,
bahwa tunangannya, Pak Samaki
had something going with you, her younger sister.
diam-diam selingkuh dengan adiknya, Nn. Hamaka?
I've known for some time that you two were on intimate terms.
Aku tahu kau berdua berhubungan intim.
And that you both eventually plan
Aku tahu kalian juga berencana
to get a hold of half of my father's inheritance.
untuk mengambil setengah kekayaan ayahku.
She also said that the manager offered them
Dia bilang manajer hotel membiarkan mereka
to use the hotel room for their rendezvous.
menggunakan hotel untuk bertemu.
Shut up!
Diam!
I know that you're letting the two
Aku tahu kau diam-diam membiarkan mereka
use this hotel for their rendezvous.
menggunakan hotel ini untuk kencan mereka.
If that's true, it can be a motive for murder.
Jika itu benar, itu akan jadi motif untuk pembunuhan.
You've got me wrong.
Itu sebuah kesalahpahaman.
Nagami just over thought things.
Kakakku berlebihan memikirkannya.
The thing is her birthday was coming up.
Ulang tahunnya sebentar lagi.
We were discussing celebrating her birthday
Kami berencana untuk merayakannya
in the suite room of this hotel that she favored.
di suite favoritnya di hotel ini.
We talked of the decorations and food.
Kami mendiskusikan dekorasi dan makanannya.
Of course, it was to be a surprise party,
Karena itu sebuah kejutan,
so it was kept a secret from Lady Nagami.
kami tidak memberitahu Nona Nagami.
We were discussing this in that room,
Karena kami bertemu di kamar itu,
so Nagami probably misunderstood.
dia salah paham dan mengatakan hal-hal itu.
She's always been the jealous type.
Dia selalu tipe yang pencemburu.
Always?
Selalu?
Yes. I used to be classmates with her in high school.
Ya. Kami adalah teman SMA,
I used to go with her since then.
dan kami sudah berkencan sejak itu.
Well, Lady Nagami really liked that room,
Dia sungguh menyukai ruangan itu,
so it's no surprise that she would get upset.
jadi aku tidak terkejut dia marah.
She liked it that much?
Dia menyukainya sebesar itu?
Yes. I hear she kicked a guest who had reservation out of the room
Ya. Dia bahkan mengusir tamu dengan reservasi
in order to spend a night there.
untuk tinggal di kamar itu.
So, we have no motive to want to kill her!
Jadi kami tak punya motif untuk membunuhnya!
We were trying to celebrate her birthday!
Kami akan merayakan ulang tahunnya!
If you still suspect us, you can ask the other staff of the hotel.
Jika kau meragukan kami, tanya staf hotel.
We talked of the decorations and other stuff with the staff too.
Kami mendiskusikan dekorasi pestanya dengan mereka.
We'll be confirming that later.
Kami akan mengkonfirmasi itu nanti.
First of all, we'd like you to tell us
Pertama, aku ingin mendengar
what you've been doing after Ms. Nagami started searching alone.
apa yang kalian lakukan setelah kalian meninggalkan Nn. Nagami sendirian.
"Next Episode" -This is an impossible crime!
"Episode Selanjutnya" -Ini sebuah tindak kejahatan yang mustahil!
Right, Takagi?
Benar, Takagi?
Where's Officer Takagi?
Di mana Petugas Takagi?
Officer Takagi's here.
Petugas Takagi di sini.
In the pool.
Di dalam kolam renang.
After the perp drowned Ms. Nagami who was searching for necklace alone...
Setelah menenggelamkan Nn. Nagami yang sedang mencari kalungnya sendirian...
It disappeared...
Itu menghilang...
Just like Conan did a while ago.
Seperti yang dilakukan Conan.
Next Conan,
Selanjutnya dalam Conan,
"Mystery Sinks into the Summer Pool (Part 2)"
"Misteri Tenggelam dalam Kolam Pertengahan Musim Panas (Bagian 2)"
Next Conan's Hint:
Petunjuk Conan Selanjutnya:
"Bubbles"
"Gelembung"
When I said bubbles in the lounge, I got champagne.
Di lounge kau akan mendapat sampanye kalau mengatakan gelembung.
Oh, no. Liquor?
Oh, tidak. Alkohol?
You're still a minor.
Kau di bawah umur.